When we are at the academy where
diamonds, thank you all. I believe that all the
team, the father, and all of you are listening. An Getty is
listening, and this is a very
interesting skill because after 10 years of working, because
in the eyes of the stars, we have to be isolated, and
finally we have seen the part about a mind
that we have gone through 36, then we have
completed 10 years of practice, and this is the 37th stage.
I feel that we are sitting and
after we have struggled with
all the realms of suffering, and
finally we have talked about the
beautiful things, the drop of water is the Bodhi mind, Bodhi, we
are the Bodhisattva. This is a television weapon
built from when they sell them
an idea, like, think,
we say, and then sell you a
car, you will come near here, and
some guy, really, he is very good, you have to know,
those things still have people catching when you
come back, you feel that it makes you
want to buy that car, but this guy,
this car seller, is he sick?
Whether or not, and he doesn't have you, do you
know, on this car with a month, it's very difficult,
I don't know, it's very difficult, and
you can hardly be.
We listen to him, look at the
pictures of Da Lat, and they understand you
immediately and write how to talk to you, it's
good and very, very
traditional in Buddhism. You sell a
very great idea, and we talk about how
it is, how great it is,
and especially in
this pinning process, we will really
enjoy it because the whole
Southern Film course is a sales job. How
we become
Bodhicitta is very great and
refreshing, and this will be a very, very
interesting summary. Today, I'm like a guy,
we will have a Special Class. After
this class, we will have a
special discussion practice between me and the contractor about the
Medicine Buddha's teachings. And it fits
into the course, how
we will return to talk about the
benefits of the Medicine Buddha practice.  I found
it very important. I'm very lucky
because I'm not a
Buddhist, so I only heard this teaching when I
was in the first class studying
Asia, then the training class on calcium, and the guy who
came here every day to buy a car had a
bookstore. I didn't know anything at
all. At that time, there were about 20 guys from
different countries, and I didn't know anything.
There were a lot of misunderstandings right from the
beginning. The
translators were very young, and Messi
said things like, "Look at the
stretcher, the neck, Tibetan, it's very
difficult." At first, I had a
lot of misunderstandings, and
we didn't talk
about it, so the understanding was very wrong. For a
few weeks, I figured it out.
I realized it wasn't like that,
and from one to mind, it's one of those words. It
took us a few months to
figure out what that word meant. Is "modi" the
Buddha's pen? When we are the
mind, each person calls it...  An
enlightened mind or working at the center of what kind of candy of
Buddhism punishes it at first, it's more than the state of
confusion so that when we, you and your family, have to
learn and have fun so that we can become a
country, right? But if
you have Bodhi mind, then you are not
at the time, and if you are having a
position of the Buddha, it's a bit, it's not
Jiangnan, it's a bit confusing for
everyone when the child suffers at the beginning, and when
the propagation of Buddhism in those
days, you don't have equipment at the beginning, that
[music]
wants to raise a child, it's a plant, it
takes half a
very long time, we can
call it, we can't deduce anything, the Buddha
wants to vomit, does it mean that the dream, the
wish to become a Buddha? From
when we mean a little bit of wanting to
become a Buddha, that's right,
that's the beginning, that's why I'm from here, the
Himalayas today, very, very, and that
week, it all made me sick with
diarrhea when running, because you
know, I  I have a strong desire to
become a part of it, and that's
what's beneficial for me. Why am I
here? They say no, no, no. It's
almost like doing this scene, it's still
a... Come on, sister, if you're really not going to do it,
then Dad will come to the heart, really?
Wait a moment, this... we
are not a mind of Buddha, will
not... and the confession of a technique
means that the salts have a mind
of each Buddha. So, is it true that I want to
become a layer, a person with a
mind, isn't it true? And
all the mortars of the people are very unlucky, and
the translators at that time could
n't speak much English, I don't
know, but I learned from people because no
one understood, didn't understand that kind of thing. At first,
what was it that we entered the essay section?
What does it mean? We have to say that
when we have a
genuine desire, we don't want to have plants,
and there's a Google question to see if
we have to have something. It has to go
back to our body,
for example, a way.  It opens us.
Or maybe we can see the set of
pain, the two of us, the two of us will you
log in, one after seeing,
meaning after that, is it a
sitting mind supermodel until 2021, now
we can see all the
contestants in the world, in this world, or
on a spaceship, all
these questions, they come down, they appear,
and we will try to
find the answer and put
first it can be said that one to mind is
not not for
bodhicitta, there are 10 points, is it selling to
talk about bodhicitta that we will
advertise because of bodhicitta, and you will start, you
will understand. This path is this point,
better, and the first way we can
approach it in the traditional way is to find
ourselves, to be a person with a single mind, how
wonderful it is, I
think that in general it is very interesting, the
retreat is very interesting because then 15
English classes in Germany covered, how wonderful it is
and many  Learning how to make a lighting system is
n't a great thing,
so how do we want to
get it and achieve it? It's not easy. They
talk about it in this retreat. We'll talk
about it in this retreat about the platform
gaining weight. What have you done in 12 years
in the cave? Can you
sleep? And they say it's
not easy. It's not like you
just go through a retreat and then
you can start. It's
something like
learning to play the piano. So we
need a lot of commitment and
time, and it's difficult. It's not like
you just get down to the initial
practice. It needs a lot of
work. You have to work, and it's
very worthwhile and very rewarding.
Van. Ten interesting things will happen
to you. The interesting things we've
talked about are the Vichy mineral springs.
Last year, we called it the thing on the teacher's body. He told
her to carry this, how much work is involved, and go
in. This is the thing.  A great teacher is an
incredible teacher who can, in
wartime, speak to ordinary people, and
what to do. Galaxy, a tree from
my time at Sera Mey Academy, one of the
best academies in Tibet.
When he was the highest superstar, the
best of all the stars,
what should be called Soccer Huarache, and besides being
drawn to, he was able to
talk to many people, so he
was very famous among
ordinary Tibetans, and even
famous people and those in the
military. Later, he was very famous,
able to talk and converse with
ordinary people, and the book he
wrote, and the teachings he taught,
were spoken to by his teachers. He was a
scholar, a writer, and a
very famous learner
today. It took about 10 years to learn
about those 60 small tables, and I believe
that this book is the greatest example
of Tibetan teaching that he ever
wrote in Tibetan, that is,
and so on. Because...  The
political issue in Tibet, that level of
language, has made it a long story. So I
can say that one of the most
valuable manuscripts written in Tibetan,
I will teach you directly from
that book, which cannot be given to you
without seeing it in order, for
those who wish to learn. Otherwise, it will
disappear, and the divine wind of my body
has taught it for 30 years and has taught it three
times. I am the assistant of
my teacher. Yes, yes,
here is an honor, only you can
hear and run into it. We have also
promoted the first advertisement on
someco, we give Coca-Cola as the great, that is the
ability and the greatest, the people with the
greatest ability, the greatest,
we talk about mothers, those who are
mothers, they have more
ability. I have never been a
mother in this weather, but I
can observe that mothers have
the ability to keep, and have the ability to
serve everyone, and they have the
ability to do more to help.  It's better
like those who have more hope, more people, and
can give up themselves for
others. My students, is there a
second Venice
happening? In Sedona, there's something
called the B virus, and
that baby is everyone having a baby.
You have to make me angry
because, and on the other hand, they achieve
something special, especially those
men. They have children, they learn
about the strangeness of life, they learn how
not to be selfish. They learn how to stop
themselves for others.
I like it. There's a guy in
that sentence, he taught for 10 years, but when he
has children, he doesn't have to put
the matter on one side, and you'll
see a completely different person. It's
like on the Mahayana path, the
middle path. When
you achieve enlightenment, when you achieve the aspiration
to become a Buddha for the benefit of
all sentient beings, then you
enter the Mahayana path, you are called a
person.  I
don't know about other classes, but the way
I grew up and the principles I taught,
but not Buddhism, there's a
history of the Mahayana path, a history of the
Theravada path, there are
different schools and different schools.
I don't know for sure, but in visa, in
Fiston, in Zintan, for reasons... It's
very difficult, it's very dry,
it's very boring. I still remember the
teachings when they were at the University of Sports.
Yeah, if you're talking about doing... If
you've slept, you'll enter
this path. If you say that, it's
not interesting at all.
It will just be
a dry school, a
dry environment, and it's
not like that, it's not that kind of
experience. The Mahayana path here
doesn't mean another school
of Buddhism or
another historical object of animals, but it
means you join a
chosen group.  The selection is very special, remember the group of
specially selected people at
DCI. There's a similar club called the
Diamond Club, and when
we have tours, there's no
world before the other one. Basically, you'll choose
5 to 6 or 10 people from each country. Those are the people who
participate in the Diamond Club,
and those are the people who are selected and checked out.
Remember, that person is from different countries,
and basically, you'll choose
10 amazing people from 20 different countries.
You book a room and the same group,
and that's a special car. What
I'm trying to say means that
you choose a country, like in
hundreds of countries, and a C100 is one in
1 billion. 2 is a C100. They look similar in
India among the population of those countries, and
you select them. Those special people from
those people, and that will be a group of
people. Reading it, it's not different. Yes, it's
very heavy. If you
get it, except for termites, it
can only be ten people from termites, one per person.  The
essence and thought, it's like the
Mahayana path. It's a club of
different people with
certain experiences, and
that certain experience is a direct manifestation of Bodhicitta. What
I want to say in the
next 15 classes is that
if you have that experience of
true Bodhicitta, you will have the experience of
jumping from this onion planet to the
planet of Dharma, from billions of planets on
the planet of the Province. You will have
another experience of moving
from the planet of the
coat and meeting
directly all the birds, all the
fish, all the human beings,
and you will meet them directly from 11 and you will
establish a commitment with them. Let's
think, let's
imagine if we jump, become
new, have a relationship with others, make
commitments, and have a personal relationship,
establishing a personal relationship within a week.
I think there must be
hundreds of billions of animals, things on
planets, but animals on...  The hand of the Lower
America planet and ask them, you will
meet them directly, you will have a connection
with them, they will be directly connected,
and you will change them
little by little, and that is the
Mahayana path. That is not a
school and of the Mahayana Party.
Mahayana means that we will have
established a personal relationship with the
billions of sentient beings and you have made
a commitment to them, similar to when
your parents make a commitment to you
to help them, and that pushes you.
You put yourself in a special club,
this is a first point of sale
about the Bodhicitta, and you can
promote Bodhicitta and will participate
in a special exclusive club. It
doesn't mean that we will
reject
others, simply if you just learn
that instruction and try to practice, try to
do something, something will
happen to you, like a true
spirit, and you will become a
Other beings of Mahayana, a little
starch, city people, the Mahayana path 1
to improve something higher,
a person closer to God,
similarly, very, very beautiful, a very
beautiful thing, a group of special people
capable of doing so, if you
sit in a class from today
to the next 10 days, it's a
completely different thought, you're closer,
closer to that. They don't teach
this at Tianjin University,
we don't learn this
anywhere else. Surely you are an
extraordinary person, close to the door of the
club of the house of light to participate
in
at Marina. You turn off the need. If you cross the line and hear
these instructions and guidance,
open your mind and heart and
listen, listen slowly, as if you can't
sit with it. This is wonderful. I
am not that kind of person, I
am not me, not special like that. I
am not one of those selfish
people, or in a billion, more than a million, ten
million, I am just a solution.  Okay, I'm not that
special, but on the third day, they were all
complaining. So, for you guys, why you?
And if you hear this
talk right now, it
proves that
you are qualified enough to
join that club. You're very close. If you
hear this talk right now,
you're very close. So
relax. I had to learn
these instructions, and try it, and it's great, great, great,
great
when we jump from one planet
to another. The nerves and
all the information and
a connection of cassava starch are connected with
them, and that's what it means,
we enjoy this Malaya road.
This is the first point of sale, the
first point of sale, talking about Morishita, a
night of conversation, the first picture, I just called it
participating, and the army, the formation, and
tennis. Ah, ah, ah, yes, yes,
the car has been free for many years at school,
trying to join the tennis club.
When I had it, it was also  There were about 10
people in there, I was about
number 10, I was new to the milk business, but in the end I
got it. It's very exclusive, an
exclusive group of very exclusive people,
and it's a beautiful feeling.
And you guys also have a way, Mom, if
you work hard you can
make that bird, and it
requires a lot of work and demands that
we work very hard. The
second benefit is, add a picture
first. We have a picture of
us when we agreed on the
university degree. A
special thing happened when I graduated from
Princeton University. At that time, I
couldn't attend the graduation ceremony
because I had to work, and
that was from when I paid off
all my loans
while buying out my medical studies. And this and
this together... and during my university years... University is
n't a ghost
job, I didn't have to attend, I
couldn't attend my graduation ceremony,
but not long after,
my friend in Mexico invited me...  I went to a
Congress, not a Congress, and this is a
11th, to a
university, a very old university in the
southern United States, and they gave
me an honorary doctorate. Now the whole
program gets the doctorate
in the middle of it, and so they, my name
is a foreign language, and I hear it, I hear it,
it sounds very strange, I'm not used to it,
and I don't have to use
that title, doctor, even though I've already
criticized the name Kashi, I hear it, but
it sounds pretty good,
it's quite a
great honor for me, and when I
go there, you wear a very
special dress, and people are very polite, and they give
me that degree, and that's the
origin of the organization, Deshpande,
and to make this story about trying to
help you, the children in Mexico, and
Ms. Tung
is clearly very great if you have
a title, a title, if it's
great if someone calls you that.  Galaxy, or
are you a journalist? And that's the second benefit
you get. You've achieved a certain level of
enlightenment, and we have the title of Bodhisattva. What is it?
Going to Sapa means you're a Bodhisattva. I don't
know about you, but the word "police
car" from Bodhisattva is incredibly beautiful.
How do you feel about it?
There's a song about Pisa, and
just the word "Bodhisattva"
sounds so sweet. We don't
know exactly what it means, but it's really
a beautiful word. It sounds so
beautiful. I'm
called a bonus, Sapa Bodhisattva. And that's the
second benefit: people will call you a
Bodhisattva. You'll have a Bodhisattva certificate,
your Bodhisattva title, and
Anh Vinh will take your name.
I know it sounds a bit strange.
We have to work very hard to
achieve enlightenment so that you can call yourself a
Bodhisattva. Bodhisattva, Bodhisattva. It
sounds a bit surreal, but it's just a
set.  So, is it
just for the title of Bodhisattva, teacher? It's a bit
expensive, but it's great, right?
Look at this. These are the things for a moment.
And this is a real thing.
Someone, if someone makes you a
coffee at 5 a.m.
Those people are definitely
Bodhisattvas, but I have to be called a
member of the club of people who
can jump from planet to
planet. I'm in the club of
people who can become this kind of person through
precise and millions of planets.
Yes, to be recognized by
people called Bodhisattvas and not to be
called Bodhisattvas. This is something,
it sounds very good, especially it's very true, it
sounds very interesting, it's surprising, I'm
very...  I'm happy to be called
Bodhisattva Day, I like being
called Bodhisattva Day, Kaycee Tien series.
Now we're going to look at the
text that has been taught for 10 years.
I've received
complaints from all of you for 10 years
about having to learn
these rules. I don't want to read this,
I don't care, just say it, it will
end. I don't care what you say,
but I
will teach you because
if you don't have a mind, it's like a
very big seed. The purpose of
this retreat is to plant a
seed in your mind. Maybe you ca
n't show a
Bodhisattva at the end of this retreat, but there will be
a seed planted in
your mind that will open up for you to
become a Bodhisattva. And if you
complete this retreat,
you will definitely have a seed that can't
stop growing. You will have
that seed and many seeds.  The
teachings will be transmitted through sound, words, and texts
from classic Asian books. And
I can say one thing:
without exaggeration or embellishment, this
is the true lineage, a lineage
that has continued for
2,500 years, for over 100 generations. It is incredibly
pure and worthy of a decisive and
astonishing achievement.
But if you are there, you will
become a Bodhisattva. These are the
accurate and correct guidance channels, and
we are honored to be in
that lineage by learning
those classical languages. You don't need to
learn English or
Chinese, but listen to it. It is an
incredibly powerful seed, and you will
experience it
much faster. Incidentally, if you
look at it
from this planet, it's not as
interesting as traveling
to another planet and encountering a
lot of other information. But you have the
opportunity to do that, and it's very difficult.
How can there be a day like this?
You have to have a
great day, put it in jail, a bad day, if
not, it's not just a beautiful day.
How can you have a
bad day when it's like a
mother carrying a promise
to her ten children? We'll
go with the text. As you wish, I have
n't, ukas. You have to get the
title of Bodhisattva Day, or Bodhisattva Day,
or Bodhisattva girl. If you have green, sour green
means Bodhisattva. If it
detects this change, it will be in your heart
[music].
In a snap of the fingers, intermodellbau
change visit possible. If you are
in 20 years or 60 years, you are
25,000.
What are you saying? Now you start to
feel you change, a chance from a
body, but not possible,
you are not, you are, but
psychologically, a person changing, another
body, a female model, meaning
those who are intoxicated with change. We call you the
deities.  Doctors,
even if you die, even if you are a
dead body,
we still call you our sons
and daughters. If you
pass away, they only have one
experience of this spiritual upliftment, and that person will say, "
Oh, that's my daughter,
my son, oh, that's my son, my
daughter." Even if you change
or you pass away, the Buddha is very
proud of you, that's my child. That
's the second benefit. And when you are called
a Bodhisattva, or when you are called, you are the
children of the Buddha, the children of the
Victorious Buddha. I am a name,
I will make a beautiful name, they will call you. Isn't it true
that you will run after and hold on, and
you will see a father hugging
his daughter?
You will not only have a piece of
paper, but you will have a political document that
says you are one of us, truly one of the
Buddha. You have a certificate, and
now you can add it.  Entering into
your title, it's not
simply that, but you will
enter a new family, you will have a new
status, I love you, I say, my school
likes to imagine this father is
a Buddha and he is embracing
his daughter or son,
a new Bodhisattva, that is, absolutely perfect,
you will have a new title, learning to
be a Bodhisattva. This has already been selected.
But
more importantly, you
become a car, meaning you
become an official daughter or son
of a family, a family is
a big family, you join
a special green family, you are a
member of that family, you are proud of
that family, just think about what it will
feel like, like the
stars, the stars that are
in the world will embrace you,
welcome you when you are a member of
our family, their family, and
for me, this is more important, I
am the title of Bodhisattva, of course you are
The Bodhisattva, but even
more importantly, you are a child,
a very special child,
and they embrace you like that, being embraced
by the Buddha, and it is also very important to call you
their child. It's about to be
a wonderful experience
like that, joining that family, being
recognized as a member of
a new family, like
stepping into a family with
animals. This is an extremely
wonderful experience, and this letter is
mentioned in the entry of the practices of
Shantideva in this part, or Bom Ca
Libor. There's a lot in the
parts of Shantideva and
in these works that talk about the benefits
of how we can
become a Bodhisattva. So yesterday, I,
Pham from California, had many
motivational quotes from
Shantideva's manuscripts. If
you can learn perfectly from
Shantideva, it's extremely important in the
difficult AE 11 11
recently.  I've received so many
questions now, I see there are so many big ones,
so many classes, so I'll ask the teacher if it's
really true that Sia and the cutting class are
starting to feel overwhelmed, and that's me,
I don't care about being overloaded, it's better
than dying, there are levels, you have to eat
as much as possible. As long as I can
feed you, you need to eat as much as possible,
especially you, a mother, need to eat as
much as possible. I'm sorry, but I
remember a moment when I was
working in fashion, diamond makeup, I
had a job at a source to
have my company and said, "Making
[music]
10,000 pieces a day, how long does it take to make 10,000 pieces of rice?"
and I said, "
About two weeks," and he said, "Why not? Is
n't it after 24 hours?" And
I
said, "Yes, can you buy it? Can you
buy 10,000 pieces in 24 hours? But
you have to tear it to be able to. Can you
ship 10,000 pieces?"  In
10 in one night, he can also
produce 10,000 items in Kim Suong in
24 hours. I like him, I started asking, "
What do you mean?" Show me
your Facebook update. It still says
that you, you, you are the manager,
right? Get out of
my office, so you will be
Bodhisattvas. You will have many
lectures. You should be happy about that.
Don't you, Thuan An, many people...
I see, haven't you handled it? You are the
managers, or are you managing it? Everything...
This is a very famous line
from CD3. This is one of the
quotes from the
Bodhisattva II.
All day today I participated in the
beautiful family of the Buddha. I have become a
child of the Buddha. And this is a
very famous line from the green
D3. This is the original version from the old days,
not the current version. They are
used in Tibetan. Translate
quickly for you. Finally, I
did something useful.  In my life
now...
Oh, you could say that I've
received a blessing. Why? Because
today I attended, I became a
member of the Buddha's family, I became a
child of the Buddha today
because I received my Bodhisattva introduction.
Now I have
more responsibilities. Should I share? I must behave
in a way that reflects
my family. I can't be a member of the
ordinary family. I can only be accepted
in my new family now. I
am in the Buddha's family, a member of the
Buddha's family, then the lineage of the
Buddha's family. Now I have a
new opportunity. I can't bring shame to
my parents' faces if I
lead in a selfish way, if I do
n't sacrifice my desires
for others. Then I will make a
picture of myself the day I join
this family. Then I promise, my brother Ba thinks
that registering and you and doing it for someone... And the
Keiko-hoshino cup is very delicious, but
you accidentally spilled the water...
In that, it's called being far from your husband,
like a trap for a girl. Children are
good children, and how will
your family be proud? Impressions in your
life, a big question, a whole
big question in your life.
Are you ready? Are you accepted
in this family or not? I don't
care if you can read
other people's minds or not. I don't care
if you can be lucky enough to be asked to smile or
not. I don't care. If you
are a PhD, then all the fields
in the world or not, even and I do
n't care if you can see the
nature of emptiness. I don't care
if you still have worries or not.
If you don't have
this attitude, if you don't call yourself a
Bodhisattva, maybe we can see the nature of emptiness,
but we can't be for
another. It can fly in the sky, but it's
not a Bodhisattva. You can be above,
but you're not a child.
You can be a chicken. We still haven't
participated in the family. Oh my
god, can we go up to the world
or not?  Whether or not to get out of this
is the question here. The next part is
different. This is a
donkey, a donkey I'm going to use to treat you.
This picture, if you manage it, can
reach a certain point in your heart.
[Music]
You can be a dog, a pig,
or as stupid as a donkey,
but you are still part of
this family. You have been accepted as a member of this
family. I like this part.
Every part of this text has meaning.
You can just get close to one thing.
This person also has this skin and Mong Cai
transmitted those parts. It's
really difficult. I chose which part is
more important. Each part in
this text shines and is
special. The text has this part, especially
because we are all human beings, we
all make mistakes. If you spend
your whole life
trying to be a good person and you
fail many times, then you start to feel like a
stupid person or, best of all,
a donkey or...  A horse. You
feel like you're a foolish person, a
spiritual fool, but you've tried
so hard, it's really, really
difficult, but you still have
bad habits that you can't give up,
or bad attitudes that you can't
give up. Some Lamas practice, they
dedicate their whole lives to sending you,
but do you feel like you're a
native? So on the day Kai bought a car, he
said that even those
who are trying so hard, so
diligently for many years to
prove themselves, and you feel that
you still haven't made much progress,
you are still a member of
this family. We have to love you, right? You
have habits,
and they haven't made beef yet, but as long
as you can jump into the shop
here and act spontaneously, then you are a
member of this family. You don't need to
be perfect to be a
member of this family. You don't need to be
perfect to be a bodhisattva. The taste of a
bodhisattva is learning to become perfect.  They are good,
but they are not yet perfect. The reason you
become a Bodhisattva is to learn to become
perfect. We love them because we
love the super-perfect Bodhisattvas. If
you are perfect and you are already a child,
you are already a Buddhist. And we will not
accept what is truly in this family.
They are already members of the family.
We want people who are perfect,
Bodhisattvas, and those who are
super-perfect or have
bad habits that they have been struggling with
for decades. And they have broken
these papers. People have been given
warmth,
meaning they cannot practice, and
their minds are lost.
We love such people
in the family, in the family of duty, the
Bodhisattvas trying to
become good people. Today
we welcome in the Buddhist family those who are
not perfect, those who want to
become perfect. That is what we
really want, those we
truly register to seek.
We will stop here today.  How about
this? You should take a break,
have a cup of coffee, or go to the
restroom, and then we'll be back in
10 minutes. We'll have a
very interesting conversation with that idiot about the practice of the
Medicine Buddha and the practice of refining the
seeds. You all, the Bodhisattvas, will be finished in
10 minutes. Uh-huh?